If on this day, Saturday, November 18th, you were like, today's the day that I'm going to decide if I'm standing with Israel or not.
Let this video be the catalyst for your decisiveness.
And as you have seen in the last couple of weeks, the fighting is very surgical.
It is slow. It is very methodical.
Surgical? What are we playing? Operation?
We are trying not to reach any of the non-combatant population in the Gaza Strip.
And I think that there is no way that we can eradicate the Hamas without dealing with most of its forces that have fled to the south.
So just so we're clear, now this is a former Israeli intelligence chief who's speaking on behalf of the Israeli government.
And he's saying that the reality is that they're going to have to keep bombing everybody because, well, Hamas is now all in the south.
The people of Gaza were told that they have to leave the north and go to the south when they dropped the little leaflets from the sky.
And as they went to the south and they were supposed to be safe, they were consistently bombarded on the way there.
So now all of a sudden, Hamas is all in the south and now we got to bomb the south.
Now, again, one little note, the non-combatant population in the Gaza Strip is really a non-existent term because all of the Gazans have voted for the Hamas.
And as we have seen on the 7th of October, most of the population in the Gaza Strip are Hamas.
This is egregiously false for a number of reasons, but one is very, very basic.
Hamas was elected in 2006 and they didn't even win the majority of the vote.
There were a number of people running and they just got the most votes.
They got 46 percent of the vote.
That was the last time there was an election.
OK, so that means that you would have to be 34 now to have voted in that election.
Y'all, over 65 percent of Palestinians are under 34.
Yeah. So the previous majority didn't vote for Hamas and the current majority didn't vote for Hamas.
So to say this is like wildly, wildly, aggressively incorrect and misleading.
And it's also just flat out evil.
So if you were still wondering, like, do I support the Israeli government or not?
Nonetheless, we are treating them as non-combatant.
We are treating them as regular civilians and they are spared from the fighting.
Do you see how the Zionist math is mathing?
Like, I really want y'all to see it.